Donald Schein Papers
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- 1966, View (Periodical), 1966 December-1967 January; nam_apap209-142 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- 1966, WHMT Internal Records, nam_apap209-143 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- 1966, WHMT Internal Records, nam_apap209-144 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- 1966, WHMT Internal Records, nam_apap209-145 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- 1966, WHMT Internal Records, nam_apap209-146 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- 1967, Diary, nam_apap209-147 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- 1967, Educational Broadcasting Review (Periodical), 1967 October; nam_apap209-148 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- 1967, Educational Television, nam_apap209-149 (Box 5, Folder 9-11)
- 1967, Estimated Cost of a Nationwide Educational Television System (Carnegie Commission Report), nam_apap209-150 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- 1967, Journal, nam_apap209-151 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- 1967, Learning From Television: What The Research Says (NAEB Report), nam_apap209-152 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- 1967, The Long-Range Financing of Educational Television Stations (NAEB Conference Proceedings), nam_apap209-153 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- 1967, NAEB Journal (Periodical), nam_apap209-154 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- 1967, Nationals Citizens Committee for Public Television -- Press Packets, nam_apap209-155 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- 1967, News Clippings on WHMT, nam_apap209-156 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- 1967, New York Network, nam_apap209-157 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- 1967, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-158 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- 1967, Return to Nursing (Broadcast), nam_apap209-159 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- 1967, Scene on 17 (Program), nam_apap209-160 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- 1967, University of the Air, nam_apap209-161 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- 1967, The View on Cablecasting and Educational Television (Periodical), 1967 April-1967 May; nam_apap209-162 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- 1967, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-163 (Box 5, Folder 25-27)
- 1968, Congressional Record of Act Creating Corporation for Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-164 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- 1968, Educational/Instructional Broadcasting (Periodical), 1968 June-1968 July; nam_apap209-165 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- 1968, Electrography Producer's Manual (Publication), nam_apap209-166 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- 1968, Financial Potential Survey, nam_apap209-167 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- 1968, Fundamentals of Television Systems (NAEB Publication), nam_apap209-168 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- 1968, Journal, nam_apap209-169 (Box 5, Folder 33-34)
- 1968, National Citizen's Committee for Public Television (NCCT), nam_apap209-170 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- 1968, Nelson Associates Study, nam_apap209-171 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- 1968, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-172 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- 1968, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-173 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- 1968, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-174 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- 1968, Scene on 17 [Program], nam_apap209-175 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- 1968, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-176 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- 1969, Annual Report, nam_apap209-177 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- 1969, CPB Annual Report, nam_apap209-178 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- 1969, Educational Broadcasting Review (Periodical), 1969 December; nam_apap209-179 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- 1969, Educational Television (Periodical), nam_apap209-180 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- 1969, Gold, Bill, nam_apap209-181 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- 1969, Journal, nam_apap209-182 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- 1969, Kettering Conference on Public Television Programming, nam_apap209-183 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- 1969, Mahrer, Neil -- Correspondence and Memoranda, 1969-1971; nam_apap209-184 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- 1969, Man is Destroying Himself: Can This Be Prevented? (Institute on Man and Science Report), nam_apap209-185 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- 1969, Membership Week Binder, 1969-1986; nam_apap209-186 (Box 6, Folder 17-18)
- 1969, NAEB Convention Report, nam_apap209-187 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- 1969, National Educational Television, nam_apap209-188 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- 1969, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-189 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- 1969, Proposal For An Instructional Television Network: Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (RPI) and Union College, nam_apap209-190 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- 1969. Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-191 (Box 6, Folder 23-24)
- 1969, Scene on 17 (program), nam_apap209-192 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- 1969, Schenectady And The Arts (Pamphlet), nam_apap209-193 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- 1969, Study of State Public TV Systems For The Corporation For Public Broadcasting (Report), nam_apap209-194 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- 1969, SUNY Course on Educational Broadcasting, nam_apap209-195 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- 1969, TV and Your Child: In Search of an Answer (TV Guide Report), nam_apap209-196 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- 1969, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-197 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- 1970, Eastern Educational Television Network Promotional Booklet, nam_apap209-198 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- 1970, Educational Broadcasting Review (Periodical), 1970 June-1970 August; nam_apap209-199 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- 1970, Educational/Instructional Broadcasting (Periodical), nam_apap209-200 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- 1970, Educational Television [Periodical], nam_apap209-201 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- 1970, Journal, nam_apap209-202 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- 1970, NAEB Press Packet, nam_apap209-203 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- 1970, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-204 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- 1970, Potential Impact of Cable Growth On Television Broadcasting (Ford Foundation Report), nam_apap209-205 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- 1970, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-206 (Box 7, Folder 7-10)
- 1970, Public Broadcasting Environment Center Pamphlet, nam_apap209-207 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- 1970, The Real World of Technical Evolution in Broadband Communications (Sloan Commission Report), nam_apap209-208 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- 1970, Report of Second EBU Workshop for Producers and Directors of Television Programmes for Young People (European Broadcasting Union Report), nam_apap209-209 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- 1970, Rochester Area Educational Television Association (RAETA), nam_apap209-210 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- 1970, Saturday Review (Periodical), nam_apap209-211 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- 1970, Scene on 17 [Program], nam_apap209-212 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- 1970, Sesame Street Magazine, First Issue, nam_apap209-213 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- 1970, A Survey of Public Television Viewing in Eight Cities (CPB Report), nam_apap209-214 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- 1970, To Improve Learning: A Report (Commission on Instructional Technology Report), nam_apap209-215 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- 1970, Volunteer Advisory Group, nam_apap209-216 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- 1970, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-217 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- 1970, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-218 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- 1971, Educational Broadcasting Review (Periodical), nam_apap209-219 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- 1971, Educational/Instructional Broadcasting (Periodical), 1971 January; nam_apap209-220 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- 1971, Educational Television (Periodical), nam_apap209-221 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- 1971, Journal, nam_apap209-222 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- 1971, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-223 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- 1971, PBS Press Packet, nam_apap209-224 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- 1971, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-225 (Box 7, Folder 29-30)
- 1971, Scene on Seventeen [Program], nam_apap209-226 (Box 7, Folder 31-32)
- 1971, Schein, Donald -- Personnel File, 1971-1987; nam_apap209-227 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- 1971, Television and the Troubled Campus (TV Guide Report), nam_apap209-228 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- 1971, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-229 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- 1972, Campaign for PBS Board of Directors, nam_apap209-230 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- 1972, The Children's Television Workshop: How and Why It Works (Report), nam_apap209-231 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- 1972, Columbia Journalism Review (Periodical), 1972 July-1972 August; nam_apap209-232 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- 1972, Educational Broadcasting (Periodical), 1972 November-1972 December; nam_apap209-233 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- 1972, Educational Broadcasting Review (Preprints), nam_apap209-234 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- 1972, Fundraiser Photos, nam_apap209-235 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- 1972, The Humanist (Periodical), 1972 July-1972 August; nam_apap209-236 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- 1972 [?], Journal, nam_apap209-237 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- 1972, Journal, nam_apap209-238 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- 1972, "Man Builds, Man Destroys" (Series Guide), nam_apap209-239 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- 1972, Marketing in Nonprofit Organizations (Report), nam_apap209-240 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- 1972, Model Neighborhood Television School, Richmond, V.A. (Report), nam_apap209-241 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- 1972, National Public Affairs Center for Television (NPACT), nam_apap209-242 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- 1972, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-243 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- 1972, North of the Namaskeag: A Case Study in Viewer-Active Television (Maine Public Broadcasting Network Report), nam_apap209-244 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- 1972, PBS Board Meeting Binder, 1972 March; nam_apap209-245 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- 1972, PBS Program Standards and Practices, nam_apap209-246 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- 1972, Program Policy, 1972-1979; nam_apap209-247 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- 1972, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-248 (Box 8, Folder 11-16)
- 1972, Scene on Seventeen (Programs), nam_apap209-249 (Box 8, Folder 17-18)
- 1972, They Got It Together: A Collection of 100 Outstanding Public Television Promotional Ideas (CPB Report), nam_apap209-250 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- 1972, Two Studies of the Audience of WJCT-TV: Jacksonville, FL, Focusing on the Viewers of Feedback (CPB Report), nam_apap209-251 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- 1972, Who Watched The Electric Company? (Children's Television Workshop Report), nam_apap209-252 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- 1972, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-253 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- 1972, National Public Affairs Center for Television (NPACT), nam_apap209-254 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- 1973, The Center (Periodical), 1973 May-1973 June; nam_apap209-255 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- 1973, Daily Notes [?], nam_apap209-256 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- 1973, The Future of Educational Telecommunication: A Planning Study (U.S. Government Report), nam_apap209-257 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- 1973, Journal, nam_apap209-258 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- 1973, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-259 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- 1973, Overview of the Office of Telecommunications Policy (Committee Hearing Report), nam_apap209-260 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- 1973, PBS National Meeting, Baltimore, nam_apap209-261 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- 1973, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-262 (Box 8, Folder 31-34)
- 1973, Public Telecommunications Review (Periodical), 1973 December; nam_apap209-263 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- 1973, Public Television Station Projected Operations and Costs (NAEB Report), nam_apap209-264 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- 1973, Rate Cards and Related Material, 1973-1986; nam_apap209-265 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- 1973, Report of the Task Force on the Long-Range Financing of Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-266 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- 1973, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-267 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- 1973, The WMHT Program Guide (Program), nam_apap209-268 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- 1973, The WMHT Program Guide (Program), nam_apap209-269 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- 1974, Community Survey: San Jose, California (CPB Report), nam_apap209-270 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- 1974, Essentials for Effective Minority Programming In Public Broadcasting (CPB Report), nam_apap209-271 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- 1974, Getting to Sesame Street: Origins of the Children's Television Workshop (Publication), nam_apap209-272 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- 1974, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-273 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- 1974, Newspaper Profile of Donald Schein, nam_apap209-274 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- 1974, NOVA Promotional Packet, nam_apap209-275 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 1974, The People's Business (Periodical), nam_apap209-276 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- 1974, Preserving the Moving Image (Corporation for Public Broadcasting Report), nam_apap209-277 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- 1974, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-278 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- 1974, Journal, nam_apap209-279 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- 1974, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-280 (Box 9, Folder 15-16)
- 1974, Public Telecommunications Review (Periodical), nam_apap209-281 (Box 9, Folder 17-18)
- 1974, Snell, DeWitt S., nam_apap209-282 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- 1974, State Of The Art: A Study of Current Practices and Trends in Educational Uses of Public Radio and Television (CPB Report), nam_apap209-283 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- 1974, The Video Implosion: Models for Reinventing Television (ASPEN Institute Report), nam_apap209-284 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- 1974, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-285 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- 1974, WMHT-FM Program Policy, nam_apap209-286 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- 1974, The WMHT Program Guide (Program), nam_apap209-287 (Box 9, Folder 24-26)
- 1975, Access (Periodical), nam_apap209-288 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- 1975, Corporation for Public Broadcasting Annual Report, nam_apap209-289 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- 1975, Eastern Educational Television Network, nam_apap209-290 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- 1975, Empire State College, nam_apap209-291 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- 1975, Journal, nam_apap209-292 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- 1975, Maday, Charles -- Memoranda, 1975-1976; nam_apap209-293 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- 1975, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-294 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- 1975, PBS Round Robin, nam_apap209-295 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- 1975, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-296 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- 1975, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-297 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
- 1975, Public Broadcasting Financing Act of 1975 (Congressional Hearing Report), nam_apap209-298 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- 1975, Public Broadcasting in the United States (PBS White Paper), nam_apap209-299 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- 1975, Public Broadcasting in the Unites States: A White Paper (PBS Publication), nam_apap209-300 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- 1975, Public Telecommunications Review (Periodical), nam_apap209-301 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- 1975, Public Television: Toward Higher Ground: Report and Papers From the Aspen Institute Conference on Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-302 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- 1975, Rotary Brochure on Schein Speech, nam_apap209-303 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- 1975, Telecommunications Policy Research Conference Proceedings, nam_apap209-304 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- 1975, TeleVisions (Periodical), 1975 August-1975 September; nam_apap209-305 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- 1975, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-306 (Box 10, Folder 11-13)
- 1975, The WMHT Program Guide (Program), nam_apap209-307 (Box 10, Folder 14-15)
- 1976, Access (Periodical), nam_apap209-308 (Box 10, Folder 16-17)
- 1975, Archaeology Project, 1976-1977; nam_apap209-309 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- 1976, Board of Trustees, nam_apap209-310 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- 1976, Day-Timers, 1976 January-1976 June; nam_apap209-311 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- 1976, Day-Timers, 1976 July-1976 December; nam_apap209-312 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- 1976, Eastern Educational Television Network -- Board Meeting, 1976 June; nam_apap209-313 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- 1976, Journal, nam_apap209-314 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- 1976, Machold, Nancy, 1976-1986; nam_apap209-315 (Box 10, Folder 24-25)
- 1976, Maday, Charles -- Notes and Memoranda, nam_apap209-316 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- 1976, NAEB Chicago Conference [?], nam_apap209-317 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- 1976, NAEB Harvard Program, nam_apap209-318 (Box 10, Folder 28-29)
- 1976, NAEB Harvard Program, nam_apap209-319 (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
- 1976, NAEB Harvard Program [?], nam_apap209-320 (Box 11, Folder 3-5)
- 1976, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-321 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- 1976, Open Education for the People (Educational Broadcasting Corporation Report), nam_apap209-322 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- 1976, PBS Informational Binder [?], nam_apap209-323 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- 1976, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-324 (Box 11, Folder 9-14)
- 1976, Public Telecommunications Review (Periodical), nam_apap209-325 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- 1976, Public Telecommunications Review, nam_apap209-326 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- 1976, Singer, Art-Notes and Memoranda, nam_apap209-327 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- 1976, A Study of Public Television's Educational Services (Corporation for Public Broadcasting Report), 1975-1976; nam_apap209-328 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- 1976, Television Quarterly (Periodical), Winter 1976-1977; nam_apap209-329 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- 1976, WMHT-FM Personnel Binder, 1976-1982; nam_apap209-330 (Box 11, Folder 20-21)
- 1976, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-331 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- 1976, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-332 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- 1976, The WMHT Program Guide, nam_apap209-333 (Box 12, Folder 2-3)
- 1977, Access (Periodical), nam_apap209-334 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- 1977, CPB Public Television Survey: On-Air Fundraising, nam_apap209-335 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- 1977, Day-Timers, 1977 January-1977 June; nam_apap209-336 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- 1977, Day-Timers, 1977 July-1977 December; nam_apap209-337 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- 1977, Desk Register, 1977-1978; nam_apap209-338 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- 1977, Development Sections Weekly Reports, nam_apap209-339 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- 1977, Educational And Industrial Television, nam_apap209-340 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- 1977, Fitzpatrick, Angela, 1977-1986; nam_apap209-341 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- 1977, Human Resources Training and Development: Selected Models for Training of Radios and Television Broadcast Personnel (Corporation for Public Broadcasting Report), nam_apap209-342 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- 1977, Instructional Television: A Study (WDSE Report), nam_apap209-343 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- 1977, Journal, nam_apap209-344 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- 1977, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-345 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- 1977, PBS Statement Before the Federal Communications Commission in the Matter of Commission Policy Concerning the Noncommercial Nature of Educational Broadcast Systems, nam_apap209-346 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- 1977, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-347 (Box 12, Folder 17-20)
- 1977, Public Telecommunications Review, nam_apap209-348 (Box 12, Folder 21-22)
- 1977, Research Guidelines for Programming Decision Makers: A Programmers Guide to the Dynamics of Radio (Arbitration Report), nam_apap209-349 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- 1977, RISE, nam_apap209-350 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- 1977, Six Experiments in Ascertainment Methodology (CPB Report), nam_apap209-351 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- 1977, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-352 (Box 12, Folder 26-27)
- 1977, The WMHT Program Guide, nam_apap209-353 (Box 12, Folder 28-29)
- 1978, Access (Periodical), nam_apap209-354 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- 1978, Capital Equipment File, nam_apap209-355 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- 1978, CPB Memoranda to Station Managers, nam_apap209-356 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- 1978, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1978 September-1978 December; nam_apap209-357 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- 1978, Educational and Industrial Television, nam_apap209-358 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- 1978, Future of Public Broadcasting Conference, nam_apap209-359 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  (Includes Audiocassette).
- 1978, Human Services Planning Council Award, nam_apap209-360 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- 1978, Journal, nam_apap209-361 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- 1978, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-362 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- 1978, NOAA Weather Radio Network, nam_apap209-363 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- 1978, Patterns of Performance: Public Broadcasting and Education, 1974-1976; nam_apap209-364 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  CPB Publication.
- 1978, PBS Memoranda to Station Managers, nam_apap209-365 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- 1978, PBS Planning Conference (Williamsburg, VA), nam_apap209-366 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- 1978, PBS Press Releases, nam_apap209-367 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- 1978, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-368 (Box 13, Folder 15-20)
- 1978, The Public Broadcasting News (Periodical), 1978 October; nam_apap209-369 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- 1978, Public Participation in Public Broadcasting (CPB Task Force Report), nam_apap209-370 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- 1978, Public Telecommunications Review, nam_apap209-371 (Box 13, Folder 23-24)
- 1978, Public TV and the Press (PBS Report), nam_apap209-372 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- 1978, Reports and Publications on Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-373 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- 1978, Saratoga Performing Arts Center (SPAC), 1978-1986; nam_apap209-374 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- 1978, Tangarone, Anthony, nam_apap209-375 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- 1978, TIAA-CREF Annual Report, nam_apap209-376 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- 1978, WMHT Auction Alternatives, nam_apap209-377 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- 1978, WMHT Board of Trustees, nam_apap209-378 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- 1978, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-379 (Box 13, Folder 32-34)
- 1978, The WMHT Program Guide, nam_apap209-380 (Box 13, Folder 35-38)
- 1979, Access, Periodical, nam_apap209-381 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- 1979, A Survey of Voter Attitudes Towards Public Television in the State of New York, Study, nam_apap209-382 (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
- 1979, Capital Equipment File, 1979-1987; nam_apap209-383 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- 1979, Community Advisory Board (?) Binder, nam_apap209-384 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- 1979, Corporation for Public Broadcasting Survey, nam_apap209-385 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- 1979, CPB Development Newsletter, nam_apap209-386 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- 1979, CPB Memoranda to Station Managers, nam_apap209-387 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- 1979, CPB Reports, nam_apap209-388 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 January; nam_apap209-389 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 February; nam_apap209-390 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 March; nam_apap209-391 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 April; nam_apap209-392 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 May; nam_apap209-393 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 June; nam_apap209-394 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 July; nam_apap209-395 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 August; nam_apap209-396 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 September; nam_apap209-397 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 October; nam_apap209-398 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 November; nam_apap209-399 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- 1979, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1979 December; nam_apap209-400 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- 1979, Endowment Committee, nam_apap209-401 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- 1979, Financial Statements, nam_apap209-402 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- 1979, Journal, nam_apap209-403 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- 1979, MHCET Financial Statement, nam_apap209-404 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- 1979, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-405 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- 1979, The Nixon Administration Public Broadcasting Papers: A Summary, NAEB Publication, nam_apap209-406 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- 1979, Notes, nam_apap209-407 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- 1979, NYS Public Television Survey, nam_apap209-408 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- 1979, PBS Legal Memoranda, Schwartz, Woods, & Miller, nam_apap209-409 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- 1979, PBS Memoranda to Station Managers, nam_apap209-410 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- 1979, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-411 (Box 14, Folder 32-34)
- 1979, Public Telecommunications Review, nam_apap209-412 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- 1979, Reports and Publications on Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-413 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- 1979, Revision of By-Laws, nam_apap209-414 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- 1979, Schein Family Photos, nam_apap209-415 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- 1979, Security, nam_apap209-416 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- 1979, State Education Department Capital Grants, 1979-1985; nam_apap209-417 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- 1979, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-418 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- 1979, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-419 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- 1979, WMHT Personal Policy Manual, nam_apap209-420 (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
- 1979, The WMHT Program Guide, nam_apap209-421 (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
- 1980, Access, Periodical, nam_apap209-422 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- 1980, Association for Public Broadcasting (APB), nam_apap209-423 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- 1980, Bromberg, Ellis, nam_apap209-424 (Box 15, Folder 8)